by the way to anyone who wants to say
over $10 million in meme coins but it's
not liquid bro it's as liquid as your
house if not more liquid if you have a
$5.7 million house and you want to sell
it you think you're going to get 5.7
million for it right away hell no you're
going to get undercut you're going to
get low balls it's going to take you
months if not a year so if you wanted to
sell your house quickly you'd have
slippage on it same thing with a mem
coin and like this position of Bret I
have here yeah at the moment it's worth
5.8 5. 7 with slippage if you want to
get out instantly you don't want to sell
you know slowly gently responsibly
intelligently you're going to lose money
to slippage just like you would on any
transaction really you want to sell your
car fast you're going to have slippage
the fact is I could get myself almost
$3.6 million liquid in a second right
now if I click a couple buttons